<vacancies>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Специалист технической поддержки</name>
        <company>Listex</company>
        <salary>22 400 грн</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Инновационной команде развития интернет-метапоиска FMCG-товаров на постоянную работу требуется Специалист технической поддержки. Необходимые навыки- Чистая,. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Tech Lead with Python Experience, Financial Software Solutions</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description>THE POSITION OFFERS REMOTE WORK OPPORTUNITY. Our client is a New York City-based FinTech Company that is building a trading and risk software platform. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>It sales specialist</name>
        <company>MELBUL LTD</company>
        <salary>13 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Requirements: Experience in selling marketing services. Sales experience with the European market. Fluent English communication. Ability to work in a multi-cultural. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Business Development Manager Bang &amp; Olufsen (Ukraine)</name>
        <company>ASBIS-Украина</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>ASBIS - ведущая международная компания, лидер рынка дистрибуции ИТ-продуктов и решений, в связи с развитием направления, приглашает на работу Business. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Програміст 1C (ERP)</name>
        <company>КТ Украина, ООО</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>«КТ Україна» - національний лідер у виробництві електроінструменту та будівельних матеріалів таких торгових марок, як Dnipro-М, Foresta, Ataman, Soma Fix. . . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior IT Solution Architect</name>
        <company>Райффайзен Банк Аваль</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>We are looking for a Senior IT Solution Architect to join our motivated, high-performing team in developing our key banking products based on modern, state-of-art. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Программист 1С(7. 7)</name>
        <company>MakeUp, Интернет Магазин</company>
        <salary>55 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Интернет-магазину косметики и парфюмерии makeup. ua, в связи с расширением штата, требуется программист1С (7. 7). Ищем сотрудника в штат компании. Основные. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Sales manager</name>
        <company>Бест Вертекс</company>
        <salary>30 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>«Best Vertex» is an international company which is mainly aimed on consulting and providing service for corporate and individual clients in IT and financial. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Аналітик бізнес-процесів/Внутрішній контролер</name>
        <company>НЕК Укренерго</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Національна енергетична компанія «Укренерго» запрошує взяти участь в конкурсі на заміщення вакантної посади Аналітик бізнес-процесів відділу оцінки процесів. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Junior C++ developer</name>
        <company>Dukascopy Bank SA</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>We are looking for: Junior C++ developer About the Company Dukascopy Bank SA is an innovative Swiss based bank domiciled and having its headquarters in. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Network administrator</name>
        <company>АШАН</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Основні функції:Обслуговування та конфігурація активного комутаційного обладнання підприємства ( Vlan, OSPF, VPN, IPSec)Обслуговування та конфігурація. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Бізнес-аналітик 1С</name>
        <company>ГК Аскания</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Група компаній «Асканія», багатопрофільний український холдинг, який включає 12 компаній різних напрямів діяльності, запрошує до команди: «Бізнес-аналітика. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Front-end developer (Angular 6+)</name>
        <company>NIX Solutions</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Харьков</location>
        <description>Мы ищем в команду разработчиков со знанием Angular 6+ для проектирования и создания SaaS-платформы предоставления услуг смарт-устройств, которая расширит. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Системный администратор (Linux, Windows)</name>
        <company>SIM-Networks</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Sim-Networks Ukraine (дочерняя компания немецкой Netversor GmbH) приглашает к себе в команду Системного администратора / Специалиста Службы техподдержки. . . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior DevOps Engineer</name>
        <company>Нова Пошта, ТОВ / Новая Почта</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Responsibilities: Working together with our R&amp;D leads to make sure dev, staging, and production are properly planned, set and maintained;Plan and maintain. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior BigData Engineer, Financial Software Solutions</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description>Our client is a New York City-based FinTech startup that is building a trading and risk software platform for the investment banking industry to sell as. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Программист-схемотехник (протокол CAN)</name>
        <company>ПОЛАРИС САТЕЛЛИТ</company>
        <salary>15 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Требования: Программист встроенного автомобильного оборудования, знакомый с CAN-шиной автомобиля;Способность написать программу под Windows для управления. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>WAY4 Expert, Global Acquiring Platform</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description>Our client is a European acquiring bank that specializes in processing Internet payments based on the WAY4 payment platform. DataArt's specialists are. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Certified PEGA Engineer</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description>DataArt is looking for a specialist with Pega expertise to maximize the potential of the Pega Platform. The client is a British-based public healthcare. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Программист 1С</name>
        <company>ВЕНБЕСТ, ООО</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Группа компаний «ВЕНБЕСТ» создана в 1991 году и на сегодняшний день является крупнейшей в Украине негосударственной охранной структурой, лидером рынка. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
</vacancies>
