<vacancies>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Junior SEO-специалист
        </name>
        <company>Lime Devs</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Мы продуктовая IT компания и, в связи с развитием новых проектов, ищем Junior SEO специалиста, который: Понимает, что такое SEO и его основные методы;Умеет...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> DevOps Engineer
        </name>
        <company>УКРОРГСИНТЕЗ, ТОВ, НВП</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> THE OPPORTUNITY Enamine is one of the main chemical R&amp;D product and service providers for the world pharma and agro-industry. IT team plays an important...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Програміст 1C (ERP)
        </name>
        <company>DNIPRO-M, ООО</company>
        <salary>45 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> DNIPRO-M - український бренд інструменту для будівництва і ремонту. Наша філософія - допомагати людям покращувати світ навколо себе. Наша місія - надавати...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Front-end developer (Angular 6+)
        </name>
        <company>NIX Solutions</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Харьков</location>
        <description> Для работы над рядом новых интересных проектов приглашаем специалистов с уверенными знаниями Angular (6+) и опытом работы.ЧТО МЫ РАДЫ ПРЕДЛОЖИТЬ:прекрасный...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Senior .NET developer
        </name>
        <company>КВЕСТ МАРКЕТИНГ ЛТД</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Key tasks:Support, refactoring, optimization and improvement of the existing codeIntegration of financial solutions and productsCooperation with international...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Production System Administrator
        </name>
        <company>Neogames</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Neogames - a leading international online lottery company is seeking a Production System Administrator.The candidate will be a part of the IT Department...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Customer Support Cоnsultant (fluent English)
        </name>
        <company>SupportYourApp</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Passionate about the latest trends in Tech? What if you had a chance to be a part of the world's leading Hardware, Software of SaaS solutions? Imagine...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Менеджер по продажам
        </name>
        <company>Бинотел, ТОВ </company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Binotel - ведущий оператор связи для бизнеса в Украине. Компания предоставляет услуги IP -телефонии с набором умных инструментов для повышения продаж и...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Test Engineer
        </name>
        <company>3Shape Ukraine</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> 3Shape A/S is a Danish hi-tech company specializing in the production and development of3D solutions (3D scanners and 3D software) for industrial and healthcare...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Senior Java Engineer
        </name>
        <company>Codeminders</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> We are looking for Senior Java EngineerRequirements:BS or MS in Computer Science or related fieldSignificant experience in Java8 (Core, Networking, RES,...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Менеджер з продажу сегменту В2В
        </name>
        <company>King Star Alliance</company>
        <salary>20 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Львов</location>
        <description> Хочеш освоїти нову сферу? Починати треба з найкращими! Не прогав свій шанс приєднатися до команди King Star Alliance в якості Менеджера з продажу сегменту...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Администратор аппаратной инфраструктуры
        </name>
        <company>Корпорация «Биосфера»</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description> Требования:Профильное образование;Знание и понимание уровней сетевой модели OSI;Опыт планирования и маршрутизации корпоративной сети;Опыт написания Fortigate...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Business Development Manager TM Canyon
        </name>
        <company>ASBIS-Украина</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> ASBISc Enterprises Plc is one of the leading distributors of Information and Communications Technology products and solutions in EMEA Emerging Markets....
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> IT System Administration Team Leader
        </name>
        <company>SMO Group</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> We are looking for a System Administrator Team Leader to be based in our Kiev office and become part of our Global IT team. In this role you will report...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Junior IT-Sales manager
        </name>
        <company>Darwin Global</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Ищем сейлза по призванию, способного «не благодаря, а вопреки» обучиться и подписывать контракты с клиентами, используя наши корпоративные методологии....
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Аналітик / Керівник підрозділу з питань протидії шахрайству
        </name>
        <company>Piraeus Bank ICB</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Ми - європейський банк, 11 років успішного бізнесу в Україні, 100 років в Європі.Регіональна мережа Піреус Банк в Україні охоплює Дніпропетровську, Київську,...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Technical Support Engineer (L2 &amp; L3)
        </name>
        <company>SupportYourApp</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Do you take pride in reproducing complex issues and finding the best solutions for customers? Are you eager to utilize your scripting skills and experience?...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Team Lead (Microsoft Dynamics CRM)
        </name>
        <company>INNOWARE</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Innoware is recognized as experts in the consulting services, specializing in ERP and CRM implementations and cloud business solutions. Our company holds...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> QA Analyst
        </name>
        <company>СимКорп / SimCorp</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description> Test Analyst for client communication and client reporting software for asset and investment management firms We are looking for a test analyst to join...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name> Senior BigData Engineer, Financial Software Solutions
        </name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description> Our client is a New York City-based FinTech startup that is building a trading and risk software platform for the investment banking industry to sell as...
        </description>
    </vacancy>
</vacancies>