<vacancies>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Embedded Software Engineer, Communications Services</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Our client is a global provider of testing, analytics, and security solutions for the telecommunications sector. DataArt's specialists are helping to develop. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>NetSuite Architect</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>DataArt is looking for experienced and motivated NetSuite Architect who could provide architecture guidance for our team in the exciting project we are. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior NetSuite Developer</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>DataArt is looking for a skilled Senior NetSuite Developer to strengthen our team which starts a new project for leading US global education provider. . . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior Sitecore Developer</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>DataArt is looking for an experienced and motivated Senior SiteCore Developer who can provide guidance and technical leadership for our team in an exciting. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>BigData Developer, Media Conglomerate</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description>DataArt is involved in the software transformation of key business areas of a US-based global music conglomerate. The solutions we're currently developing. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>IT manager</name>
        <company>Citizen development</company>
        <salary>30 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>IT manager ФОРЕКС Опыт работы в Форексе минимум 6 месяцев Работа с объемом от 40 человек Возраст до 30 лет Работа с Linux , windows , IP телефония, Опыт. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior BigData Engineer, Financial Software Solutions</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Our client is a New York City-based FinTech Company that is building a trading and risk software platform for the investment banking industry. The BigData. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Customer Support Consultant (German/Polish/Spanish/Korean/French/Italian)</name>
        <company>SupportYourApp</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Micro-mobility is the future of travel. Agree? Are you passionate about mobile devices for moving around the city and modern technologies? Join our team. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior React Native developer</name>
        <company>NIX Solutions</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Харьков</location>
        <description>Наша команда ищет Senior React Native developer, который возглавит разработку мобильного клиента с чат ботом под iOS / Android. Проект - система взаимодействия. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Менеджер по продажам</name>
        <company>LOPAN group</company>
        <salary>15 000 грн</salary>
        <location>Харьков</location>
        <description>LOPAN group», 15 лет продаем, внедряем и поддерживаем программные продукты «1С», «M. E. Doc», «LIGA:ZAKON», знаем абсолютно все про электронный документооборот. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Data Scientist / BI Analyst</name>
        <company>Factum Group</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Data Scientist / BI Analyst - в динамично растущую команду Factum Group Требования: Высшее образование: computer science, data science, статистика, маркетинг. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior/Lead . NET developer</name>
        <company>Edsson Ukraine LLC</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Требования: Experience with Azure, ASP. NET MVC, Entity Framework, SQL Server or NServiceBus are considered assetsBachelor's degree in (Applied) Computer. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Программист 1C</name>
        <company>РАЙСЬКЕ ДЖЕРЕЛО, ДП</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>«Райське Джерело» (https://www. eden. com. ua/) - ведущая компания на рынке Украины в направлении Aqua-service (доставка и производств бутилированной воды. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Головний фахівець з інформаційної та кадрової безпеки</name>
        <company>Укргазвидобування, АТ</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Потенційний пошукШановні кандидати, у зв'язку з карантинними запобіжними заходами співбесіди проводитимуться онлайн або після закінчення карантину. Забезпечувати. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>. NET Senior (Middle) Developer</name>
        <company>ISM Ukraine</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Житомир</location>
        <description>Looking for a full-time job in the Zhytomyr office?Then you should definitely take a look at our vacancy! ISM Ukraine is the Ukrainian R&amp;D of the Dutch. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>WAY4 Expert, Global Acquiring Platform</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Our client develops solutions for acquiring payments. They have created a global automated online payment platform that specializes in the processing of. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Senior BigData Engineer, Financial Software Solutions</name>
        <company>DataArt</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Днепр</location>
        <description>Our client is a New York City-based FinTech startup that is building a trading and risk software platform for the investment banking industry to sell as. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>System Administrator (with scripting) / DevOps</name>
        <company>Onseo</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>We're looking for a person to join our team with a strong system and technological background who we'll be responsible for supporting large, international. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Customer Support Manager (EN + DE)</name>
        <company>JavaRush</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Интересуешься ИТ, любишь и умеешь общаться с людьми? Грамотно формулируешь свои мысли в письменном виде и обладаешь стрессоустойчивостью? Можешь помирить. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
    <vacancy>
        <name>Angular Developer</name>
        <company>Epom</company>
        <salary>Не указано</salary>
        <location>Киев</location>
        <description>Epom is a cross-platform ad-serving platform for ad campaigns management, monitoring and optimization. Epom provides customers with a unified platform. . .</description>
    </vacancy>
</vacancies>
